and I came back stayed a little longer
and then went to a sales job made 40
Grand and I
bounced um I was like peace you know and
then in this crappy apartment that was
in the best neighborhood that you could
possibly be in so you know but it was
mine you know so what are like do you
are you facing those pressures right now
or are your parents you know or your
mother or whoever are they
supportive of
you putting the puzzle pieces
together um well uh I did have that
conversation with my mom actually um
which is what motivated me which is
another thing that motivated me to be an
entrepreneur because um we had the
conversation you know of
um what would happen if the if in the
event that she that something happen
what if there was a docu series for
entrepreneurs that never ended a living
documentary that will continue to
clarify illustrate and unfold
information about the culture that
surrounds
entrepreneurship what if this docu
series was filmed in front of a live
audience all over the world where
censorship and editing were no longer
applicable when information that is
given to you isn't packaged but
delivered to you raw and fresh honest
and truthful what if you could ask
questions live or help fact check while
someone is speaking well we have already
created this platform and we call it
hustle Zone TV
[Music]
and we are oh that was really hot
um and we are live holy
moly this is the first show that I've
done um in 2018 for the hustle zone so
I'm actually super duper
excited
wo this is the hustle Zone folks and um
and I'm your host Ryan Perez I'm so
happy so um if you guys uh can you guys
do me a favor I'm going to do this right
now I want you guys to share share share
share share because um sharing is
caring I'm going to make honest to God
I'm gonna make a song called sharing is
caring for the hustle
Zone um so what's up Benjamin Benjamin
says Hi how are you doing my friend um
so I'm asking everybody to share so I'm
going to go into my own video
hold on a second but I can't hear myself
um how was the audio folks like can you
guys hear
me okay yes I I think that the audio is
good is good we just we're back and
there's some technical cuz I I had moved
my office upstairs and then I've moved
it back hold on a second I got to turn
this down I moved it back downstairs and
the software everything stopped working
so um
I am you know so we're just having some
technical difficulties Etc but the you
know honest to God it's okay I mean it
it it happens
um I am super excited for tonight and uh
we we do have a special guest and he he
is a guy that he's we've been trying to
get him on but for whatever reason um
you know the um
the cosmos did not want me to bring him
on so um you know we are attempting to
do this again and um I would love to see
your guys's comment on the screen so you
guys bear with me we are still working
out the technical
difficulties uh with the comments but um
um needless to say we will get the
comments in in a few minutes um but um
I'll tell you a little bit about my
guest now my guest he's a multi he's a
ser he's he's he's he's a
multimillionaire no he's not a
multimillionaire but he's a he's a um he
he is telling me in the green room um
that he's soon to be a
multi-millionaire and um you know and
and and and I think you know like we all
start somewhere um and uh he's he's I
would say that he's an aspiring
entrepreneur um he has three different
businesses um one which that I'm really
curious about and um he says it's
billionaires under construction um he
really wants to promote um more black um
uh wealthy entrepreneurs that are
billionaires because there are not a lot
of them out there and you know what that
is so true so we are going to talk about
that and we're going to talk to him
about um his life I mean you guys know
how I roll on the hustle Zone
um we we we uh we get deep you know we
we ask hard questions because you know
what that allows people to understand um
the entrepreneur or to connect with the
entrepreneur so um you know we are
definitely going to be asking him some
of the hard questions you know because
especially I like to do that with with
with with guys that are starting out
because you know you really want to you
want to see like what is the drive I I'm
curious I always want to know what what
is the inner drive that causes people to
do what they do you know um because
maybe that inner Drive can Inspire
someone you know or their story can
Inspire someone to to take action and
that's that's what it's it's it's it's
all about um and I just want to say a
special shout out to we got Miss
zanadoo um and I don't know if it's
going to come up okay it looks like the
comments are just not going to come up
so um I just can't do it today um you
know the technical difficult
difficulties are um causing me not not
to be able to respond um the way that I
would like to so um that's okay so we're
just going to take this off and we we
are just going to do a normal show so
either way
folks I want you guys to put your hands
together for Mr David Williams how are
you doing David finally
hey fourth time David was like man you
pissing me
off I don't want to be on your show oh
hold on a second here let's see there we
go we got your audio in there but he's
like he's all David's all pissed off he
don't want to come on the show cuz Ryan
I was cuz I was sick during the time
that you're supposed to be on a show
wasn't feeling well and then we had
technical difficulties there's all kinds
of things that happened and then booked
again and all that stuff but finally are
you excited to be on the show yes I am
I've been looking forward to it man for
a while so thank you for having me
that's awesome that's awesome and I've
seen you in the shows I've seen you
participating in um
um I I've seen you participating in um
Monica's show and then you know in a few
of my shows and um you know you you seem
very proactive and and uh so the first
question I'm going to ask you now I want
you to start from the very beginning um
and normally
I um normally I ask this question to all
of my guests no matter who you are
whether you're a billionaire or an no
may I don't know um you know what is
your story so start from the very
beginning like when you were a child all
the way like where were you born you
know what happened at school you know
give me as much um as you're willing to
defa all right so um before I got you
know to this point of being an Entre
which for one I I love what I do um
before I got to this
point
um I struggled with that I I struggled
with you know trying to figure
out what was it that that I wanted to do
not what other people wanted me to do
you know and not uh living up to the
expectations of other people but what
did David want to do you know and it
took um
until I was about 25 which is when I
made the decision to become an
entrepreneur and my my decision uh came
from um you know I I just got to a point
where I just got tired I got tired of
being at the mercy of other people when
it came to work you know and finding
jobs and um and most of my jobs were
seasonal you know I I never was able to
have like a consistent job you know even
though I did what they said I did
everything that they asked me to do and
uh I had a conversation with with one of
my friends about that you know and I got
on the phone with her and I said like I
hate my job I I hate being at the mercy
of other people so I started um looking
into like books you know how to write a
book and I was already expressing myself
on Facebook you know to begin with um
and I had wrote this one um book about
not book I'm sorry about post about um
astrology because I I do study that
stuff I had to do study astrology and
numerology and finding out as much about
yourself as possible so that way nobody
else can come along and tell you how you
should be so I wanted to know as much
about myself as I possibly could so I
wrote um like one or two posts about
astrology and um people were really
really into it and they liked it so from
there I graduated from Face from post on
Facebook to
blogging um now blogging was a little
bit more personal I blogged about you
know stuff that I might have seen out in
the street or something like that um and
then again my astrology blogs got most
got most of the views you know and so I
kind of took that as a sign um that
maybe I should start off with writing a
book uh and and it does help to have
friends who support you so one of my
friends uh she liked what I wrote about
in the blog and on Facebook so she put
the bug in my ear for me to write a book
now initially I wasn't going to uh
because I wasn't
sure um what people would say or how
they would take it but I kind of took it
as the universe or the powers that that
be um this was then pushing me in the
direction of you know becoming an author
and writing a book um and then to add on
to that um another
thing that motivated me to do all of
this was my grandfather because my
grandfather was an entrepreneur him
himself you know and I had the
opportunity to go see him um when he
passed like after he passed initially I
wasn't going to go uh because one I like
to be around people that are vibrant so
being in a funeral is not vibrant so I
was going to keep my distance but you
know I said you know what to pay my
respect I'm going to go
anyway
and it made sense on why I want to do so
much stuff because my
grandfather had three or four things of
pone that he did
so um hey David um I don't mean to
interrupt you but um would you mind
you're you're on a
laptop yeah can you tilt the camera so
that your head is more closer up to the
top of the camera because there's a lot
of white space there oh no the other
way there we go that's awesome okay all
right so continue your story thank you
no problem no problem
um yeah so my grandfather was played a
big part in me becoming an entrepreneur
because he
did three or four things of his own you
know he invested in real estate he had a
nonprofit himself he had a to um a TV
repair shop and then he also had a
construction business so he did three or
four things of his own and um the only
regret you know that I have is not being
able to be mentored by him you know it I
feel as though um although I'm doing you
know pretty well on my own I feel as
though I would do even more damage if I
was um if I if it was a grandfather
grandson Mentor mentee kind of
relationship
um so that's how I got to this point you
know my my grandfather played a big part
um in me making the decision to become
an entrepreneur because after I found
out all that he
did you know it was kind of like all
right grandpa I get it you know and I'm
Gonna Keep The Torch going until it's my
time to pass it so that was my
motivation for wanting to be an
entrepreneur okay so now um how was your
how was your childhood um how did you
grow up because I'm already Hearing in
your
voice that and just I'm just hearing you
got a little attitude you know what I
mean
you really yeah you got you have a
little tinge of just wanting to do
things on your own and where does that
like I I don't know I I'm pretty
intuitive but what am I sensing here
because I think that you know cuz I
think all entrepreneurs just have that
attitude that like I don't want you
telling me what to do you know you're
working at chuckecheese like I used to
work at Chuck-E-Cheese and you know uh
I'm sweeping and they're like sweep
faster and you're looking at him like
yeah yeah you want me to sweep you know
what I mean so you getting all mad and
stuff but you know but what's you know
you have a little bit of Independence in
your you know just just hearing you talk
you seem to be very particular about
your your your Independence so like how
did you grow up in high school or you
know like just going up through school
you know were you the popular guy were
you the you know uh were you the guy
that had his head in the books like were
you picked on were you not picked
on um actually I and I'm glad that you
picked up on that I I respect that I
really do
um I was I was the quiet kid in in
school you know I I stayed to myself um
I had a few friends you know two or
three um but for the most part I stayed
to myself you know because I never
really needed a whole lot
of people you know around me I I was
always just comfortable with two or
three friends um so I was fairly quiet
in school you know I didn't talk a lot
um even at home you know sometimes I
didn't talk a lot either at home you
know but when it was time for me to say
something I'd say something and um and a
lot of
times I don't like to be rough
you know so um I prefer to again like as
you hinted on do things when you know I
when I personally feel the time is right
not having to worry about you know
keeping up with other people or whatever
the case may be um and I do I I do like
to be very uh independent I do uh and
that was initially when I got into
entrepreneurship that was
my uh downfall that was my downfall
because I felt
like whatever I took on I could do you
know it didn't matter what it was
whether it was three four five six seven
different things I felt like I could do
it so I kind of just took my chances and
did it and did it you know and uh one of
my favorite models or quotes is you know
they told me I couldn't so that's why I
did you know so that's always been one
of my favorite quotes you know and
[Music]
um yeah in school I was a quiet kid you
know so when I really got into writing
books or perfume or whatever it is that
I'm currently doing it kind of shocked
people you know
because they were so focused on me being
quiet you know they were so focused on
um me staying to myself that they didn't
expect that from me they didn't expect
me to grow up and do that um and I like
giving people the wow factor I really do
you know like when um people don't
expect me to do something and then I do
it and then I go ahead and do it anyway
so I I just kind of like that that
feeling of giving people uh The Vow
Factor
um I didn't have can I ask you a
question sorry I don't mean to interrupt
but were you ever doubted um Beyond you
know just for the fact that you know
that people MH um know you're quiet
but have you ever been doubted for your
ability because no one really wants to
proes anyone
wrong unless they've been doubted unless
they've been pushed around unless
they've been someone's been pressing on
them to do so because like I'll I'm an
open book I was that person a lot of
people doubted me because I was clumsy I
was messy um I there was a lot of things
that were wrong with me and I'm and I'm
dyslexic but I'm also I'm a dyslexic
with a high IQ
so it it was really tough for me to go
to school my teachers used to dump my
desks on the you know on the floor when
it was messy and embarrassed me in front
of all the kids so when you talk to the
kids if whatever they remember me they
remember me being a bad kid being sent
to the office or being having my desk
dumped so you know I'd be walking home
from school being like I'm going to show
you you know what I mean I i' have
dreams about Michael Jackson pick me up
in his limo I'm like like one of these
days you know Michael Jackson's gonna
come and pick me up
so and and reason why I bring that up
because you know it's it I don't think
what we're I hear aggression I like
maybe I'm wrong I'm picking up on
something and I'm not sure what I'm
picking up on but I know that this is
deeper you wanting to prove this you
know because I'm realizing I don't have
to prove anything to anybody but wanting
to prove prove something to somebody and
giving people a surprise or W factor
that has to come from somewhere it
doesn't just come because you want
to that that's true um for a while I was
uh I was teased myself so that's that's
common ground um I was teased myself
um you know people used to go out of
their way
to
um you know to kick my book bag or or
you know to take something out of my
locker when I wasn't looking um so to
answer your question yeah I did um I'm
getting to that point um like you were
just saying of you know not having to
prove it to
people um because I I feel as though you
know I've done a lot before the age of
30 um which today is my birthday uh
happy birthday David thank you so I as
though I at this point um within the
four years that I've been you know on
this journey as an entrepreneur um I've
done a lot before the age of 30 so I
feel as though now I don't have anything
to prove I can kind of you know just
kind of chill out a little bit at least
a little bit now will I always have
ideas most likely but but at least I
don't have a chip on my shoulder anymore
and it took a long time for me to get to
that point you know because um because I
had people tell me that I couldn't do
stuff you know it took me um initially
especially with like writing and stuff
like that it took me a little bit longer
than everybody else to do stuff you know
and um writing in particular um so
initially I had people telling me you
know I can't do this I can't do that and
initially yeah I did I did have a chip
on my shoulder do I now know you know
because I've um even though it took me a
while to get here I
found things that work for me and things
that let me um express myself freely you
know and be as honest as I could
possibly be and that was my whole um
thing about school you know was that I
felt as though you know working for
other people or in school
rather I could not be free to express
myself the way that I wanted to and so
that was another motivation for me
wanting to become an entrepreneur
because I
saw people that were living life how
they wanted to with nobody telling them
what to do or anything and um aside from
my grandfather motivate motivating me to
do it that was another motivation you
know was the freedom that comes with
that and that I didn't have anybody over
me or having to having to answer to
anybody of course we'll have to listen
to somebody so I won't say that yeah but
uh but as far as having to go and tell
somebody like hey I did this hey I did
that like having to constantly tell
somebody what I'm doing I don't have to
do that and that was another motivation
for why you know I got to this point
of wanting to be an ENT preneur so to
answer your question yeah I did I I did
for a while have a chip on my shoulder
do I now no no I've kind of Let It Go uh
but for a while I did I did have a chip
on my shoulder yeah because the the
process is really humbling and I mean it
didn't take I I like I didn't take the
full plunge to entrepreneurship until
2013 and because I had no I had no other
recourse I mean you know I was a
managing partner of a marketing company
lost my job because the partners wanted
me out and
um you know I you know I went home and
my you know my my fiance at the time her
and I were having issues and then she
left so I was kind of forced into it and
uh you know I had no other
recourse now and I didn't want to go
back cuz I was working retail jobs and
all this other stuff I didn't want to go
back to all of that so it it was pretty
tough for me I I had a chip on my
shoulder because I was like you know
what I know I'm talented you know I've
made other people money I've done I've
worked for these companies and they've
took all my ideas and how come I can't
use these ideas for myself and build a
life for myself you know so it was
pretty aggravating um to say the least
and I still have a chip on my shoulder
um but um you know but you you got to
start you have to it doesn't matter when
you start you just have to start now I
made a joke earlier you know off in the
green room because currently right now
you live with your mom is that
correct that's true okay so and I'm not
calling you out but I think that that's
what the hustle zone is about that's
what you're not going to get on
everybody else's uh show is that I I'm
going to ask the tough questions because
I think it's necessary to see
everybody's different lifestyle
and and how like you know show people
their the full story instead of hearing
a narrative you know showing the full
story because where you start is not
where you're going to end how does like
in the position that you're in with your
businesses right
now are you happy where you're at at
this given moment are you working hard
to get to the next level in your life
um I am working hard to get to the next
level you know
because
um don't get me wrong you know I love my
mother to death but um I feel as though
it is time for me to
um kind of spread my wings you know so
to speak um so I feel as though um am I
happy semi yes am I happy completely no
because I've been hit by this bug of
wanting my own stuff you know and
um it's a work in progress of course
like with any business or anything that
that we're doing um
so I am happy to a
degree but not as much as I would like
to be so that's why I do so much stuff
you know and I have no plans on slowing
down
because I feel like anything that I want
to that I set out to do I can do you
know and I'm not leaving that up to
other people to decide I've decided that
for myself
so um so it's answer your
question no not completely it it's
partly you know partly and I love my
mother to death but no not completely no
now i' have to be honest I again I can
tell you I've had humble beginnings um
all through my life you if you were to
look at me when I was 20 you would not
see the same person and I just recently
posted my you know my first
manifestation my first Manifesto um my
goals and stuff like that that I wrote
when I was in it was in 2001 I'm 34 now
I was 17 then
um I but I knew there was a genius in me
I just knew it I knew my ideas I knew
that I helped people I knew that I could
do something but at the same time I
didn't know because I've never
accomplished
anything um I knew that like I was
really shy and but I knew I was
aggressive I mean I knew I was very
direct
but it was hard to I just didn't come
into myself so what makes you
think Mr
Williams what makes you think that
you're going to be a billionaire or a
millionaire or like what is giving you
this inclination that you're going to be
successful
entrepreneur well for one because you
know I look at um you know past
billionaires and past successful people
and I think a lot of times you know when
you hear like the term billionaire a lot
of people are for whatever reason um
intimidated by the thought of just
becoming a billionaire and when I was uh
when I really started doing my research
and finding out you know which people I
wanted to study whatever the case may be
I wasn't intimidated I was inspired
because I felt like it's been done
already so I I felt as though uh I could
kind of add my Nam to those to those
ranks or those or those numbers however
they say it um so I wasn't I wasn't
intimidated by like the idea of becoming
a a billionaire I just I just wasn't you
know because and plus again like I
mentioned in the beginning of this
interview um my grandfather was a big
thinker too so so knowing that he was a
big thinker uh it just motivated me
myself to be a big thinker as well um
but I didn't again I didn't start off
want uh with aspirations to be a
billionaire um I started off you know
working like I told you a a couple of
odd jobs by working at Macy's by working
at Michaels and a couple of retail jobs
um but I found people to study on the
side when I wasn't home I mean when I
was at home forgive me um I found people
to study you know and I started looking
into the Warren Buffett's
and the Jay-Z's and and the p diddies
and I really started to study them you
know and find out what it was that they
did that got them to that point of
billionaire status did you say Warren
Buffett yes okay Warren Buffett is my
guy okay so tell me about Warren Buffett
what is it about Warren Buffett that
inspires
you um for one um like you just hinted
on a minute ago him being humble you
know the fact that he is worth I think
what 63 billion or a little bit more I
could be wrong I could be wrong and he
still drives the same car that he drove
when he started and he still lives in
the same uh I'm guessing house or
apartment or wherever it is that he
lives um despite being worth 63
billion I thought that was um
respectable you know and and I want to
get to that point where I am as humble
as Warren Buffett and it doesn't matter
what um I aspire to have I will always
be thankful for people that um that have
helped me in this position that have
motivated me to do something or whatever
it is you know I will always be thankful
to some degree because I understand that
I'm not a oneman show right although I
am the you know the front runner when it
comes to like this dream that I'm
building and
everything I am not a oneman show it's
not just me by myself you know there are
people that have come along um like
yourself and Monica and a few others
that have helped me to get the word out
about my story or or interested in my
projects or whatever it is so I
understand completely that uh it's not
about me at the end of the day you know
I'm at the end of the day I'm just the
messenger that that's it you know I'm
just um I was given a specific
assignment or a specific
and I'm going to see it through whether
I become a billionaire or not I'm going
to see this through because I feel like
this was something that I was given you
know and I'm just I just believe in it
that much you know that um anything that
I want to do I can do and I'm going to
take my at this point I'm just going to
take my chances you know I'm not uh
leaving it up to other people to decide
when
it's my final time or when it's my final
business or whatever it is not even Dr
Phil because I've seen Dr Phil have you
ever watched Dr Phil Dr Dr Phil will be
like you know what you're never going to
be a billionaire because you know what I
mean like I I've seen him do that and
you know especially if you're not
bringing in the money or you're not
paying the rent or whatever even parents
come down and say hey like you know I
understand you have
dreams but you got to pay these bills we
got to kick you out or we got to put you
you know have you been faced with that
you know with with some the pressures of
life um the pressures of family trying
to get you to move
along you know because I've been told
you know I was living with my dad till I
was I think uh I forget I don't know
what my age was but the uh you know my
mentor would say you know what bird
doesn't leave the nest is a dead one and
you know that was you know that in
itself was enough for me to just get out
and I had to find a way out I left and I
came back stayed a little longer and
then went to a sales job made 40 Grand
and I
bounced um I was like PE you know and
then in this crappy apartment that was
in the best neighborhood that you could
possibly be in so you know but it was
mine you so what are like do you are you
facing those pressures right now or are
your
parents you know or your mother or
whoever are they
supportive of
you putting the puzzle pieces
together um well uh I did have that
conversation with my mom actually um
which is what motivated me which is
another thing that motivated me to be an
entrepreneur because um we had the
conversation you know of
um what would happen if the if in the
event that she that something happened
to her or or if she passed or something
like that we had that conversation and
that's what I was trying to explain is
is that most jobs are not loyal they're
not loyal nowadays they're they're just
not because
um when I first got started in all of
this um you know she asked me what am I
going to do in the event that she passes
and
uh I had already had it had it in my
mind made up that entrepreneurship was
what I was going to do because that was
my backup you know and we we talk a lot
about having a backup plan um so
entrepreneurship was my backup you know
and I saw that I saw a pattern with with
my jobs I saw that most of my jobs did
not last any more than five months for
whatever reason and I again I did what
whatever it was that they asked me to do
you know but for whatever reason they
just did not last whatsoever you know
and
so um to answer your question yes I have
been faced with that which is excuse me
which is what put me in this position
you know right now because we did have
that conversation
of what would happen if in the event
that something you know was to happen to
her or something like that so we did
very much so we did have that
conversation and again
after she asked me that my mind was
already thinking about starting
businesses because I want uh something
to pass down that's my whole thing you
know I I want something that that I can
pass down whether it's books whether
it's fragrances whether it's wine or my
nonprofi I want to pass something down I
I just what what is your um because one
of my lessons that I've had in um
because I've been chasing my tail for
many years I mean four years is when I
just actually like figured it out I was
like oh
shoot and it's been when I was 30 I was
I was you're 30 now right yeah so just
around that time when I was 30 that's
when my life that that year I swear that
that like the very moment it was in
November very moment I turned 30 like
everything all the events leading up to
that I I was starting to make money and
all kinds of things and I was scared to
turn 30 because I'm like I am I'm not
[ __ ] I I don't know who I am I I I I
don't know and then when I turn 30 I'm
like okay this is cool I like this I'm
an adult but you know
the reality for you is
that you got to bring in cash flow
because because one of the the one of
the one of the biggest lessons that I
had to learn because I read Rich Dad
Poor Dad thinking girl rich and you know
read the secret read all these books and
you know I just never really got it I
really never really put things forward
because I was always in the planning
stage because I'm analytical it takes me
forever to plan things out but you yeah
like I you know like I I I don't really
like I never thought I was smart but
it I turned out to be you know really I
I I I figured that with myself I'm just
more more intelligent than I thought I
was so it took me a long time to get to
even just where I'm at now so what is
your view on cash flow and don't do you
believe that without because like if
you're not bringing in I'm not sure what
your cash flow is like right now but do
you believe that you're going to need
that you know because how long do you
have to
just you know let things kind of fester
like how long are you going to wait for
you to start actually bringing in the
castle so that you can take yourself
from point A to point B because that was
a lesson and I hate to like I'm not
lecturing or anything like that it was
just a lesson that I I had from a friend
who was in business and he was like Ryan
you know you're going to lose your girl
if you don't bring in the cash flow and
I'm like man who you talking to I'm I'm
going to make it I'm going to be a
billionaire millionaire whatever and you
he was so right because I lost her that
year I lost her twice you know and this
was in
2009 um and then I lost her again and it
was it was crazy um and it was like you
know she was my best friend right
because I wasn't bringing in the cash
flow so what's your feeling about cash
flow at this point and how can you
amplify yourself so that you can get out
and be independent
um well for one
my I've been um and this this is another
reason why um you know I've started off
with books you know
because with books I don't necessarily
have to be awake for somebody to buy one
and I was big on um finding out more
about you know passive income which I'm
I'm sure you know about and the people
that watch this they know about that
yeah um I was big on passive income you
know
because I wanted something that that
would make
it
um a little bit
easier um so that way while I'm
making money from books I could use that
to do other stuff right I didn't want to
be confined mind to just being known for
books you know even though books is what
I started off doing I love that
um but right now because I'm not because
my job is is closed
um books is what lets me make money from
my
perfume because and that and that's why
I didn't just stay with books you know
because I get that question quite a bit
you know um because people who don't
understand it will think
that will think that I'm jumping around
not
realizing not realizing
that I've done two books already and I
and I'm devoting a little bit of my
energy to something else right because
you know what I'm saying so uh even
though in the midst of that I'm working
on a third book and on the outside
looking in it may look like
I'm just chasing my tail I'm just
chasing a Tail Feather and chasing my
tail I know what I'm doing you know
because I understand that
books takes time to build you know and
it takes that's why I focus when I'm
focused on the book that's what I'm
focused on but once I finish my books um
I try to find like other ways around it
you know to make money which is how I
got into fragrances right um you know
and so
although I was initially I was telling
you you know about about wine and
fragrances and books and other stuff
that I'm speaking into existence
um books is definitely the foundation
that's why in the midst of everything
I'm still finding a way to work on a
third book and a fourth book because
that's my right now that's my Foundation
because uh if I if I was just working a
job and I was just dependent on my job I
wouldn't be doing any of this you know
and that's just the honest to God truth
I wouldn't be um doing any of this so I
started using the the money that I get
from my job to buy books to buy
um um fragrances to buy books to buy
fragrances so I
started planting the seeds for other
stuff I didn't
just and plus I didn't want to be in a
position where I have to worry you know
and and that's why I do so much you know
even though go ahead can I can I ask you
something
um oh before I ask that can you lower
your volume down a tad bit because
sometimes I hear an an echo and I know
my voice is
loud but
uh
but uh
yeah can I ask you you're like you know
because like and and it sounds like you
have an action plan and um like I said I
was was your age when I kind of
kickstarted my life and started coming
into money the first time in my life so
you know um so it's like again it's
never too late to like kind of
accelerate um especially when you have a
foundation like your books um what makes
you special like what what is your what
is your
superpower um to the reason why you are
going to be um successful you know I
would say that for me it's my
determination and my intellect
um but for you what would you say would
is your
superpower um my superpower I like how
you put that I like that um my
superpower honestly I I I have to say at
this point um is the ability to be calm
but like my my determination for what it
is that I want is like through the roof
you know I don't um this setbacks of
course their setbacks but I I I don't
take no for an answer you know I I I
want I want what I want you know and I
feel as though um and it took it took a
while you know for me to get to that
level of confidence it took a while it
didn't I wasn't born with it I wasn't um
it took a while for it to build you know
but I feel as though like my personal
superpower is the ability to be mellow
and calm and have people
um feel comfortable with me but my but
my determination for what I want is
through is through the roof you know I
don't um like I said I don't take no for
answer when I want something um it may
take a while for me to get what I want
but I do get what I want eventually um
so I feel as though like that's like my
personal you know super
power that's awesome and I think you
know you're you're pretty methodical and
you think things through you know so
it's not like um you know you can be
rattled against your idea of becoming
successful um but you know I hear you
know you have a seriousness about what
it is that you want to do and it and and
I think that's great I think that's a um
you know it's a great attitude to have
because like this year you know 2018 I'm
saying hey I'm going to make a million
dollars this year period absolutely I've
never made million dollars but this year
2018 is going to be the day so every day
I'm coming on camera and I'm like you
know half of me is
like you know I'm okay with $100,000 you
know what I mean or I'm okay with a
$200,000 or whatever it is um but um you
know the reality is is that I know I can
make more um and I had to readjust my
company I had to do a lot of different
things just to get myself in alignment
to my goal but you got to start with
that manifestation you have to start
with you know thinking about what it is
that you want to accomplish and I
applaud you that you have a good
awareness a self-awareness about how
you're going to go about it and the fact
that you do study others to do you you
know you're admitting to yourself that
you're humble you yourself are humble
you you know you're taking your time and
I think that you know people in your
life trust you you know I I think they I
think they trust you because they know
you're not going to misuse your time
or you're not going to slack off you're
really going to make this happen so you
know I applaud you for that now when it
comes to like if I if you had a Magic
Brush right
now who would you
be you know what I mean like what what
would you do to yourself and to your
life like give me what that vision would
be wait can you ask the question again
because it was kind of low okay sorry if
you had a Magic Brush you know and a
magic magic wand and you could just zap
your life into whatever you wanted it to
be besides being an entrepreneur because
the entrepreneur kind of helps you
achieve those
dreams what would
you what would you be you know and who
would you be what would you have you
know and where would your money
go um
my money honestly would go to
um or at least part of it you know
because underneath underneath all the
ambition and the determination and all
that stuff at the end of the day I like
to have fun you know that's that that's
definitely something that
um attracted me to entrepreneurship as
well you know is the ability to
eventually have fun you know I don't
want to be one of those people that just
works works works and works and works
and never has fun never laughs never
jokes with
anybody
um um so if I if I was if I had a magic
wand I would
uh and I and I I call this the Superman
effect if I could be anybody I'd be
Superman because
Superman could do anything he could do
whatever he wants and
of course you know he kind of has to fit
in with everybody eventually but um
but when it's time for him to go to work
he can do whatever he wants you know he
can take off the suit and tie and just
fly away you know so uh and that's
honestly how I felt when I got started
with all the stuff that I'm doing you
know I felt at work I was very much
suppressed I I couldn't express how I
felt the way I wanted to and and when I
got into when I got into other stuff
like speaking in books and fragrances
and um in wine or whatever it else that
I'm involved
in I got addicted to the feel of it
because I I ultimately had free reign I
ultimately
had I wasn't restricted by anybody I
didn't have to go to anybody to tell
me
so so then what would you do with your
freedom though because now you're
begging the question what would you do
with your freedom like would you have a
boat with like like a bunch of beautiful
women on it partying drinking booze and
doing drugs like what is freedom to you
like what would be you know if someone
gave you Freedom what would you be doing
with
it um well if I had freedom uh I'm big
on traveling I'm big on I love to travel
you know and that's just just um that's
just my spirit I love to travel you know
I don't like to feel as though I'm being
confined so if I had the money to do
so I would just get up and go on a
flight I would just get up and and go to
London to Paris to Barbados wherever it
is that I want to go so that's part of
where my money would go you know because
again um I grew up on traveling I used
to go on cruises and all of that stuff
so I'm kind of spoiled kind of spoil
when it comes when it comes to traveling
because now that I'm old enough to do it
myself I want to go everywhere I want to
go to London I want to go to Paris I
want to go to Tokyo I want to go
anywhere anywhere that my mind allows me
to go you know so I I feel as though if
I had the money to do so that
that's with no question that's where my
money would go it would go to traveling
um if people want to come along that's
great but but that's where my money
would go it would go to traveling
because I love to travel yeah now um and
that's awesome I think you know being
able to use your money to go and see new
things and and and whatnot um you know I
think everybody wants to do that some
people want to stay home some people
want to party do drugs whatever it is
that they their heart you know leads
them right um but you know you you had
said something interesting in the preall
that you know you want to
inspire young black youth right to
become billionaires so tell us a little
bit about
billionaires um in construction or in is
it in construction uh under under
constru I like billionaires in
construction yeah we we Carpenters but
we billionaires though we welders but we
billionaires though so billionaires
under construction okay so tell me about
that
um billionaires under construction it
came from again like we were talking
about uh before we got on
camera uh I was just going off of an
observation you know and I felt as
though
that um even though salutes all the
white billionaires salute to them but I
feel as though it's not it's not even
you know there's a serious lack of
colored billionaires there's or at least
from what I've seen you know um there's
definitely a serious lack and again you
know this is just to match up with what
my grandfather was doing because my
grandfather had a nonprofit as well and
he his nonprofit dealt with um I think
teenagers that are at risk I think I
could be wrong but he definitely had a
nonprofit um so I kind of wanted to
match that
you know and I started really doing my
research on billionaires since that's
since that's where I want to be I
started doing my research and I noticed
that there's not a lot you know there's
um definitely some Chinese ones and some
Caucasian ones but there's not a lot of
billionaires that look like us so that
was my motivation for me wanting to do
it
now have I started started building the
foundation for that I have um I started
working on a website um I started you
know developing my business page for
that but that's something that I'm going
to devote more time to later on like
later on down the road um but I but
again I'm planting the seeds for it now
so that way once I'm at that point I
already have my website set up I already
have my um business page set up I
already have certain things set up so
that way it's just about
connecting with people you know it's not
so much about putting in the groundw
work it's about connecting with people
um so that's where the motivation for
that came from you
know it was on my heart for a while um
because if anybody talks to me um
underneath all the ambition and all of
that
stuff my heart is charitable you know
and so um I kind of wanted to come up
with an outlet that reflected that
you know and so uh that's where the
motivation for that came
from well I I think that's I I again I
think it's awesome I think that you you
sound like you have a steady you know a
steady understanding of where you want
to be and and how you want to help
people and um I never gave up on my
dreams it sounds like you're not going
to give up on yours and um you know it
was a a pleasure to have you on the
hustle Zone because again um my intent
with this was to get you know someone
you know like I wanted to get people
from different spectrums of Life all
telling their stories and realizing that
all of us have similar you know habits
and similar Ambitions when it comes down
to it you know entrepreneur you're not
when you you decide that you want to be
an entrepreneur you're an entrepreneur
for life you're an entrepreneur for life
you don't it doesn't change right you
know and you'll never forget it so you
know the fact that you want your freedom
but you also want to help it people I
really find that admirable and I I I
again thank you so much for for sharing
your story and allowing me to be Ryan
Perez and you know do what we do on the
hustle zone right and it's be real and
ask those real questions um we got a
part two of this uh before we before we
U end the show um so it's our lightning
round lightning round
um we're gonna ask like a you know rapid
round questions of different random
stuff so are tomatoes a fruit or
vegetable fruit is a fruit okay um who's
your favorite who's your favorite Harry
Potter
character Ron
Weasley is your bird calling you
yes she does that sometimes wow that's
amazing um have you ever stolen
anything I
have
what I have he's like I have I'm just
not gonna tell y'all okay perfect do uh
do you think anyone considers you a
hipster no okay what's the sound you
make um if you're
freezing these questions man what's the
sound you make when you're freezing
cold sound I make it from freezing
cold
um I don't make a sound that's I had
never heard that question that's yeah
that's weird ass question don't I didn't
write the questions folks I didn't write
the questions but I do cuss I'm
like turn on that goddamn heat you know
like I'm over here like you know I don't
like the code I can't function in the
code like my house is 32° I don't know
what that means in fight or whatever but
like it is hot it's like Jamaica weather
in my house all the time um uh when
eating formal a uh when eating a formal
meal with multiple Forks do you start
from the outside or the
inside I start from the inside and why
do you start from the inside
um I don't know it feels like to me it
feels um strange like to start from the
outside in so I just it feels like a
straight line like if I go from left to
right it kind of feels like a straight
line so that's why that's why I do it
okay um what's your favorite martial
art my favorite martial art kickboxing
kickboxing LA or New York
I grew up in New York so I'd have to say
la I was expecting you to say New York
okay um Michael Jackson or
Prince oh that's a tough one bro um
Michael
Jackson artha Franklin or Anita
Baker
artha okay Justin timlake or Luther
vanross
I see what you did there man I see what
you did there um Luther Luther okay um
scale from one to 10 how good at you at
are you at
trivia wait what was the question um
from scale from 1 to 10 how good are you
at
trivia on a scale of 1 to 10 I give it a
eight eight okay um Super Mario Brothers
or
Zelda Super Mario Bros if Tupac appeared
before you right now what's the first
thing you would ask
him
um that's a good
one um
I'm not sure I'm not sure you're not
sure you just look at him be
like wait hold on a minute say it again
say it again what's the first question
you would ask Tupac if he said Tac I'm
alive oh Tupac okay yeah
um What mo well if I had to ask him a
question I probably ask him uh what
motivated him to go to
um to go to dance school I think that's
one of the things that he did so I would
want to find out like more information
about um what motivated him to do
that yeah like Tupac were you crazy Mr
Thug going into a dance school no I'm
joking okay and the last question is
what temperature do you like your
thermostat
at uh what temperature do I like my
thermostat at
um well I like spring weather so I'd
have to
say like 65 like 65 degrees 65 degrees
okay and oh and last question is it
wrong for a vegetarian to eat animal
crackers
um no I don't think that's
wrong okay sounds good well that's the
right lightning
round and then we're going to do uh so
thank you so much for participating in
the hustle Zone folks um we're back uh
so if you guys want to book a show we
got to start screening these calls
because like you know sometimes we get
requests from people and we're like whoa
Mama um but um you know definitely we
definitely want to see you we want to
hear from you so hit me up if you want
to be on the show we do not hold back we
want to know you more than what people
generally know about you that's our our
our style um so you can catch us at
hustlez own.tv and then um also check
our sister company where we build
websites we do graphic design all that
good stuff BC creative.com so David how
was your experience on the hustle
Zone uh my experience um on the hustle
Zone was great you know I I felt
uh because I understand that chemistry
is important so I felt that there was
good chemistry there I do you know uh
and if I'm allowed on again hopefully um
we can actually do a a part two you know
where I can go like more in detail once
my nonprofit and my one businesses are
like set up like maybe we could focus a
little bit more on those um because
those right now like I said are Works in
progress um so like maybe one they're
actually set up like we can go more in
detail with those for sure well you're
always welcome um you know and uh you
know good luck with everything and with
all the businesses that you have and I
wish you all the best you know and I and
I and I truly mean that because you know
I think that um again you're an
entrepreneur for life and you you
obviously enjoy what you do and you
enjoy being in the space that you're in
and you know as long as you're having
fun and enjoying enjoying that process
then everything is going to work out for
you so I wish you the best of luck thank
you so much David for coming on to the
hustle zone so before you leave one more
thing that you have to do is do a call
and response and a call and response I
go um when I say no I'm joking
um uh I'm GNA say welcome to the and I
need you to scream it loud I want your
mom to be like what kind of interview
was that okay okay so all
right one two three welcome to the
hustle zone no no no no no
no try try try it again okay you got to
scream it loud I mean you got to disturb
the piece because this is just a this is
a tradition everybody did this you know
from Top every episode we've had people
do this so let's do it one more time
or whenever how long it's going to take
me to get you to scream from the top of
your lungs okay one two three welcome to
the hustle
Zone what the hell is that that is
nothing what you me what the hell is
that what you mean you got to scream it
loud it has to be loud I got to hear the
vibrations I got to see it red
line try it one more time
welcome to the hustle
Zone see Z you gotta give me some credit
You Gotta Give me some all right you
gotta give me some
crit okay all right sounds good well
David it was a pleasure having you on to
the show and and again I hope you had a
really good experience and know I
enjoyed having you on I I really I
really like your like your thought
process and and you know when you said
Warren Buffett you had me at Warren
Buffett so um you know if you if what if
if Warren Buffett is what you who you
look up to then you're in good hands um
so I wish you luck with all your
business Endeavors and I'm sorry that we
took us four tries to get onto the show
but you know what we're here and um you
know and thank you so much uh so uh I'm
going to let you go now but
folks like wow
that was great I I think that was
awesome I think you know and I hope that
you guys don't really think that I go to
grill certain people over other people
the reality is is that you know um I
like interviewing everybody and
there's every story no matter how
successful you are you could have so
much money and be so busy and not have
family or friends you know like me you
know what I mean you're you're busy
you're doing successful and stuff like
that I don't really have friends I don't
really have everybody has you know an
opposite to what it is that they're
doing and I usually find that and I ask
about it because that's the stuff that a
lot of us
think but a lot of us don't ask and you
know entrepreneurs are it's almost like
we're Immortal you know
because we don't because of the fact
that we know we're going to be
successful there's nothing you can say
to bring us down unless you start
talking about my big forehead because I
don't know how
long you could talk about my big
forehead and where I just start I
shutting
down but I honest to God you know it's
always good to hear people's thought
process because that's how you know that
that they're that they're going to be
successful it's just you know how
methodical they're thinking how they're
thinking things through and you know
who's supporting them what are the kind
of um members in and around them that
are really giving them the influence and
I didn't really get a chance to ask our
our guests about that today but you know
I do I do wish him all the best I think
this was a great show um and he gave us
really good um he gave us really good
content um so you know make sure you
guys follow him um and I'm going to
bring him back on here tell me where can
we get
you okay
um my Instagram is uh it's the same as
my nonprofit right so my Instagram is
billionaire under construction um you
can find me on Instagram uh I have a few
business pages on Facebook um one of my
business pages is blissful Memories by
ky's which is uh which is my wine brand
that I'm that I'm working on it's my
wine brand yeah uh I also have a page
for my fragrances which which is Kyle's
fragrance
LLC uh and then I also like I said I
have the nonprofit page as well so
billionaire under construction is also a
business page and then I'm also on
Twitter uh my Twitter is
uh billionaire
bzr Blazer it's blazer for sure
billionaire
Blazer and then I'm also obviously on
Facebook and wants to add me they could
um so my name on there is
David uh d a v i d k a y l e z Williams
w i l l i a
Ms and I'm always on so if anyone
reaches out to me like I'll message them
back I'll accept the requests I'm always
on awesome and um folks you guys can
find me at hustle Zone TV you can find
me anywhere and then I have a personal
blog where I post my vegan food my crazy
Antics and um you know my son I am a
vegan I am a father I'm a
goofball um and I'm an entrepreneur um
so you guys can definitely check me out
at RP the God you know what I mean and
don't ask me why I call it that because
you don't want to have that discussion
today um but yeah you guys want to
follow me hustle own TV we are the
world's first living documentary um we
just collect stories of entrepreneurs we
add it to our website we add it to our
collection we have two shows that we're
going to be producing pretty soon and a
third show on the way we're just in
negotiations in discussions at this
moment so um you guys want to check it
out and then of course you guys can see
my
Vlog on my path to road to a
million you know I'm going to tell you I
don't really like I don't really like
that blog I really don't because I don't
like airing out my dirty laundry and I
don't like airing out my inner thoughts
about certain subjects but we know we
got to do it last year I did it with my
weight loss journey and I was doing six
push-ups and I was embarrassing but look
at me now I got no more man titties
remember you guys used to see my man
titties
on you you guys used to see it on uh on
um you know like in my lives right and I
would comment on it I don't got those no
more you know why because I never give
up on my dreams just like David you know
we just keep it moving keep it moving
and uh we uh we make it happen I am who
I am who I am who I am you know and I
make no apologies for it um you know I I
love this community because this
community gives me so much Vibrance and
gives me so much energy and gives me so
much positive um reinforcement to
continue to do what I do
and you guys are the reason why the show
is you know why we have the hustle Zone
you know you guys keep me going so thank
you guys all for your support Susan day
zanadoo Greg marks uh Peter D all Nick
Harris all those people that have come
into this show thank you so much for
appearing and of course we're gonna we
we um we're going to thank Our Guest
David Williams he has tree jobs tree
businesses so you know um I'll I'll talk
to you later and make sure you guys um
you know if you guys have any people
that you know would want to be on the
show um tell them to hit my assistant up
Lindsay I will give uh you know just
send me a message and we'll get it all
um she's going to be doing the bookings
for the show now um uh we used to have
the bookings on the show but we have to
screen we have to screen our our our
interviews because some people that have
signed up for not people that I would
personally have on the show um and um I
I'm just looking for inspiring people
people that have positive out looks and
you know like like our guest David so
you know either way thank you guys so
much I love y'all talk to you later road
to a million doll road to a million do
road to
million Ryan's G to get before
bye what if there was a docu series for
entrepreneurs that never ended a living
documentary that will continue to
clarify illustrate and unfold
information about the culture that
surrounds
entrepreneurship what if this docu
series was filmed in front of a live
audience all over the world where
censorship and editing were no longer
applicable when information that is
given to you isn't packaged but
delivered to you raw and fresh honest
and truthful
what if you could ask questions live or
help fact check while someone is
speaking well we have already created
this platform and we call it hustle Zone
TV
[Music]